var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "إِذَا",
        "answer": "When",
        "pcklId": "400",
        "rootWordId": 27,
        "tlit": "idhā",
        "frequency": 409,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " إِذَا زُلْزِلَتِ الْأَرْضُ زِلْزَالَهَا",
        "rootWord": "إِذَا",
        "rootWordType": "nominal",
        "wazn": "إِذَا",
        "waznEnglish": "when",
        "waznTlit": "idhā",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Time adverb)",
        "waznFreq": 409,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "459",
        "rootWordId": 32,
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": 461,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " إِذَا زُلْزِلَتِ الْأَرْضُ زِلْزَالَهَا",
        "rootWord": "أ ر ض",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أ ر ض",
        "waznEnglish": "the Earth, land",
        "waznTlit": "hamza rā ḍād",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 461,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْأَرْضُ",
        "answer": "the earth",
        "pcklId": "460",
        "rootWordId": 32,
        "tlit": "l-arḍu",
        "frequency": 461,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَخْرَجَتِ الْأَرْضُ أَثْقَالَهَا",
        "rootWord": "أ ر ض",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أ ر ض",
        "waznEnglish": "the Earth, land",
        "waznTlit": "hamza rā ḍād",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 461,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "الْإِنْسَانُ",
        "answer": "man",
        "pcklId": "92",
        "rootWordId": 78,
        "tlit": "l-insānu",
        "frequency": 97,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَقَالَ الْإِنْسَانُ مَا لَهَا",
        "rootWord": "أ ن س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "إِنسَٰن",
        "waznEnglish": "you perceive",
        "waznTlit": "insān",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 71,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَثْقَالَهَا",
        "answer": "its burdens",
        "pcklId": "11",
        "rootWordId": 205,
        "tlit": "athqālahā",
        "frequency": 28,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَخْرَجَتِ الْأَرْضُ أَثْقَالَهَا",
        "rootWord": "ث ق ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ثَّقَلَان",
        "waznEnglish": "(will be) heavy",
        "waznTlit": "thaqalān",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 6,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْقَالَ",
        "answer": "(equal to the) weight",
        "pcklId": "23",
        "rootWordId": 205,
        "tlit": "mith'qāla",
        "frequency": 28,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " فَمَنْ يَعْمَلْ مِثْقَالَ ذَرَّةٍ خَيْرًا يَرَهُ",
        "rootWord": "ث ق ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مِثْقَال",
        "waznEnglish": "(will be) heavy",
        "waznTlit": "mith'qāl",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 8,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "مِثْقَالَ",
        "answer": "(equal to the) weight",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "rootWordId": 205,
        "tlit": "mith'qāla",
        "frequency": 28,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 8,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَنْ يَعْمَلْ مِثْقَالَ ذَرَّةٍ شَرًّا يَرَهُ",
        "rootWord": "ث ق ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "مِثْقَال",
        "waznEnglish": "(will be) heavy",
        "waznTlit": "mith'qāl",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 8,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "تُحَدِّثُ",
        "answer": "it will report",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "rootWordId": 297,
        "tlit": "tuḥaddithu",
        "frequency": 36,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " يَوْمَئِذٍ تُحَدِّثُ أَخْبَارَهَا",
        "rootWord": "ح د ث",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "تُحَدِّثُ",
        "waznEnglish": "to report, to narate",
        "waznTlit": "tuḥaddithu",
        "waznType": "Verb (form II)",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَخْبَارَهَا",
        "answer": "its news",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "rootWordId": 385,
        "tlit": "akhbārahā",
        "frequency": 52,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 4,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " يَوْمَئِذٍ تُحَدِّثُ أَخْبَارَهَا",
        "rootWord": "خ ب ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَخْبَار",
        "waznEnglish": "your news",
        "waznTlit": "akhbār",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَأَخْرَجَتِ",
        "answer": "And brings forth",
        "pcklId": "151",
        "rootWordId": 397,
        "tlit": "wa-akhrajati",
        "frequency": 182,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 2,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَأَخْرَجَتِ الْأَرْضُ أَثْقَالَهَا",
        "rootWord": "خ ر ج",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَخْرَجَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to bring forth, to drive out",
        "waznTlit": "akhraja",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 99,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "خَيْرًا",
        "answer": "good",
        "pcklId": "152",
        "rootWordId": 449,
        "tlit": "khayran",
        "frequency": 196,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " فَمَنْ يَعْمَلْ مِثْقَالَ ذَرَّةٍ خَيْرًا يَرَهُ",
        "rootWord": "خ ي ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "خَيْر",
        "waznEnglish": "they select",
        "waznTlit": "khayr",
        "waznType": "Nominal (Noun)",
        "waznFreq": 178,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَرَّةٍ",
        "answer": "(of) an atom",
        "pcklId": "36",
        "rootWordId": 506,
        "tlit": "dharratin",
        "frequency": 38,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " فَمَنْ يَعْمَلْ مِثْقَالَ ذَرَّةٍ خَيْرًا يَرَهُ",
        "rootWord": "ذ ر ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ذَرَّة",
        "waznEnglish": "and their descendents",
        "waznTlit": "dharrat",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 6,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "ذَرَّةٍ",
        "answer": "(of) an atom",
        "pcklId": "37",
        "rootWordId": 506,
        "tlit": "dharratin",
        "frequency": 38,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 8,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَنْ يَعْمَلْ مِثْقَالَ ذَرَّةٍ شَرًّا يَرَهُ",
        "rootWord": "ذ ر ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ذَرَّة",
        "waznEnglish": "and their descendents",
        "waznTlit": "dharrat",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 6,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَهُ",
        "answer": "will see it",
        "pcklId": "264",
        "rootWordId": 523,
        "tlit": "yarahu",
        "frequency": 328,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " فَمَنْ يَعْمَلْ مِثْقَالَ ذَرَّةٍ خَيْرًا يَرَهُ",
        "rootWord": "ر أ ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَءَا",
        "waznEnglish": "to see",
        "waznTlit": "raā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 271,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يَرَهُ",
        "answer": "will see it",
        "pcklId": "265",
        "rootWordId": 523,
        "tlit": "yarahu",
        "frequency": 328,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 8,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَنْ يَعْمَلْ مِثْقَالَ ذَرَّةٍ شَرًّا يَرَهُ",
        "rootWord": "ر أ ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَءَا",
        "waznEnglish": "to see",
        "waznTlit": "raā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 271,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "لِيُرَوْا",
        "answer": "to be shown",
        "pcklId": "312",
        "rootWordId": 523,
        "tlit": "liyuraw",
        "frequency": 328,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " يَوْمَئِذٍ يَصْدُرُ النَّاسُ أَشْتَاتًا لِيُرَوْا أَعْمَالَهُمْ",
        "rootWord": "ر أ ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَرَيْ",
        "waznEnglish": "to show",
        "waznTlit": "aray",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 40,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبَّكَ",
        "answer": "your Lord",
        "pcklId": "966",
        "rootWordId": 524,
        "tlit": "rabbaka",
        "frequency": 980,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " بِأَنَّ رَبَّكَ أَوْحَىٰ لَهَا",
        "rootWord": "ر ب ب",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "رَبّ",
        "waznEnglish": "the Lord",
        "waznTlit": "rabb",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 975,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "زُلْزِلَتِ",
        "answer": "is shaken",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "rootWordId": 625,
        "tlit": "zul'zilati",
        "frequency": 6,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " إِذَا زُلْزِلَتِ الْأَرْضُ زِلْزَالَهَا",
        "rootWord": "ز ل ز ل",
        "rootWordType": "quadriliteral root",
        "wazn": "زُلْزِلُ",
        "waznEnglish": "to shake",
        "waznTlit": "zul'zilu",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 3,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "زِلْزَالَهَا",
        "answer": "(with) its earthquake",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "rootWordId": 625,
        "tlit": "zil'zālahā",
        "frequency": 6,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 1,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " إِذَا زُلْزِلَتِ الْأَرْضُ زِلْزَالَهَا",
        "rootWord": "ز ل ز ل",
        "rootWordType": "quadriliteral root",
        "wazn": "زِلْزَال",
        "waznEnglish": "and they were shaken",
        "waznTlit": "zil'zāl",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَشْتَاتًا",
        "answer": "(in) scattered groups",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "rootWordId": 755,
        "tlit": "ashtātan",
        "frequency": 5,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 4,
        "arabicAyah": " يَوْمَئِذٍ يَصْدُرُ النَّاسُ أَشْتَاتًا لِيُرَوْا أَعْمَالَهُمْ",
        "rootWord": "ش ت ت",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَشْتَات",
        "waznEnglish": "separately",
        "waznTlit": "ashtāt",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 2,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "شَرًّا",
        "answer": "evil",
        "pcklId": "24",
        "rootWordId": 767,
        "tlit": "sharran",
        "frequency": 31,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 8,
        "wordnum": 5,
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَنْ يَعْمَلْ مِثْقَالَ ذَرَّةٍ شَرًّا يَرَهُ",
        "rootWord": "ش ر ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "شَرّ",
        "waznEnglish": "(is) bad",
        "waznTlit": "sharr",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 30,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يَصْدُرُ",
        "answer": "will proceed",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "rootWordId": 827,
        "tlit": "yaṣduru",
        "frequency": 46,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " يَوْمَئِذٍ يَصْدُرُ النَّاسُ أَشْتَاتًا لِيُرَوْا أَعْمَالَهُمْ",
        "rootWord": "ص د ر",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "يَصْدُرُ",
        "waznEnglish": "to proceed",
        "waznTlit": "yaṣduru",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 1,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلْ",
        "answer": "does",
        "pcklId": "273",
        "rootWordId": 1022,
        "tlit": "yaʿmal",
        "frequency": 360,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 7,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " فَمَنْ يَعْمَلْ مِثْقَالَ ذَرَّةٍ خَيْرًا يَرَهُ",
        "rootWord": "ع م ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَمِلَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to do, to work",
        "waznTlit": "ʿamila",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 276,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "يَعْمَلْ",
        "answer": "does",
        "pcklId": "274",
        "rootWordId": 1022,
        "tlit": "yaʿmal",
        "frequency": 360,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 8,
        "wordnum": 2,
        "arabicAyah": " وَمَنْ يَعْمَلْ مِثْقَالَ ذَرَّةٍ شَرًّا يَرَهُ",
        "rootWord": "ع م ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَمِلَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to do, to work",
        "waznTlit": "ʿamila",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 276,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَعْمَالَهُمْ",
        "answer": "their deeds",
        "pcklId": "346",
        "rootWordId": 1022,
        "tlit": "aʿmālahum",
        "frequency": 360,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 6,
        "arabicAyah": " يَوْمَئِذٍ يَصْدُرُ النَّاسُ أَشْتَاتًا لِيُرَوْا أَعْمَالَهُمْ",
        "rootWord": "ع م ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "عَمَل",
        "waznEnglish": "and do",
        "waznTlit": "ʿamal",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 71,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "وَقَالَ",
        "answer": "And says",
        "pcklId": "1613",
        "rootWordId": 1245,
        "tlit": "waqāla",
        "frequency": 1722,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 3,
        "wordnum": 1,
        "arabicAyah": " وَقَالَ الْإِنْسَانُ مَا لَهَا",
        "rootWord": "ق و ل",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "قَالَ",
        "waznEnglish": "to say",
        "waznTlit": "qāla",
        "waznType": "Verb (form I)",
        "waznFreq": 1618,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "النَّاسُ",
        "answer": "the mankind",
        "pcklId": "233",
        "rootWordId": 1530,
        "tlit": "l-nāsu",
        "frequency": 241,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 6,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " يَوْمَئِذٍ يَصْدُرُ النَّاسُ أَشْتَاتًا لِيُرَوْا أَعْمَالَهُمْ",
        "rootWord": "ن و س",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "ن و س",
        "waznEnglish": "the people",
        "waznTlit": "nūn wāw sīn",
        "waznType": "Noun",
        "waznFreq": 241,
        "hasRootWord": true
    },
    {
        "question": "أَوْحَىٰ",
        "answer": "inspired",
        "pcklId": "71",
        "rootWordId": 1595,
        "tlit": "awḥā",
        "frequency": 78,
        "surahnum": 99,
        "ayahnum": 5,
        "wordnum": 3,
        "arabicAyah": " بِأَنَّ رَبَّكَ أَوْحَىٰ لَهَا",
        "rootWord": "و ح ي",
        "rootWordType": "triliteral root",
        "wazn": "أَوْحَىٰٓ",
        "waznEnglish": "to reveal, to inspire",
        "waznTlit": "awḥā",
        "waznType": "Verb (form IV)",
        "waznFreq": 72,
        "hasRootWord": true
    }
]; 
export default words;